<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Prestley Heights Townhomes HOA Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Prestley Heights Townhomes HOA Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright> </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Parking lot striping to be rescheduled</title>
      <link>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/parking-lot-sealing-2021-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/parking-lot-sealing-2021-2/</guid>
      <description>Our small parking lot had its asphalt sealed this morning, but due to this afternoon&amp;rsquo;s rain, the striping and parking block installation is being rescheduled. I&amp;rsquo;ll make another post when I have a new date.
Thanks to all who cooperated with getting parked vehicles clear of the area. The contractor tells me it shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be driven or parked on for two days, so I&amp;rsquo;ll remove the cones and tape on Friday (August 13).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parking lot sealing and striping</title>
      <link>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/parking-lot-sealing-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/parking-lot-sealing-2021/</guid>
      <description>The contractor selected by the board of directors for the asphalt sealing of our small parking lot has scheduled the work for Wednesday, August 11, 2021 (weather permitting). The work will also include painting lines and installing parking stops, which should make for a clean, well-maintained look for our parking area.
Pictured above: Our small parking lot.
As a result, we&amp;rsquo;ll need all vehicles to be removed from the area for the work to be completed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mailbox electricity - August 2021 Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/mailbox-electricity-august-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/mailbox-electricity-august-update/</guid>
      <description>Just as a quick update on the mailbox electricity project:
The electrician we had contracted with in the spring was unable to get the wires under the road. A part for the tool being used was broken in the process and he had ordered a replacement. Since then, we&amp;rsquo;d been simultaneously waiting for that replacement part to arrive while also seeking potentially a different contractor to help with getting conduit (for wire) under the road.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sidewalk repairs and asphalt sealing</title>
      <link>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/sidewalk-repairs-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/sidewalk-repairs-2021/</guid>
      <description>Sidewalk repairs The board has approved hiring a contractor (Big Bear Concrete Leveling) for some minor sidewalk repairs. This includes a place near the entrance of the townhomes where a sidewalk segment is no longer level with the ones adjacent to it, and a few segments that have significant cracks / crushing visible.
Work is scheduled to take place this Friday, July 23, and is expected to be completed during the same day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updates from the Board of Directors</title>
      <link>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/dog-waste-station-size-upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/dog-waste-station-size-upgrade/</guid>
      <description>Dog waste station upsize In response to feedback received during the annual meeting, the board agreed to upgrade the size of the dog waste station container. The previous size was 10 gallons and the bigger size (now installed) is 22 gallons. The ongoing costs of emptying were unchanged as a result.
The one on the left is the prior, smaller size. The one on the right is the one currently installed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retaining counsel for research</title>
      <link>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/collier-chartiers-retaining-counsel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/collier-chartiers-retaining-counsel/</guid>
      <description>Dear homeowner:
As you may have heard during our annual meeting on April 29th, we are exploring the idea of having our townhomes included as part of Collier Township / Chartiers Valley School District to align with the rest of the Prestley Heights community.
In order to determine the benefits, drawbacks, legal processes, and likelihood of success, the board is planning to retain a law firm for a cost of up to $2,500.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Board of Directors 2021-22</title>
      <link>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/board-members-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/board-members-2021/</guid>
      <description>Revised May 28, 2021.
Per the announcement made during the annual meeting, we have a newly elected member of our board of directors. Likewise, an appointment was made to fill the seat vacated by a prior board member, and titles have been determined. The list of board members for this term is now:
 Matt Condio - Vice President Brian Finn - Secretary (newly elected) Benn Linger - President Robb Williamson Max Nogay (board appointed)  Brian would like to share the following message:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring 2021 Updates</title>
      <link>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/spring-2021-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/spring-2021-updates/</guid>
      <description>A few quick updates to our homeowners&#39; association members:
The mailbox power project is expected to continue late this week or early next week. The bit on the boring tool our electrician was using got burned up in the process, so he&amp;rsquo;s ordered another that&amp;rsquo;s expected to arrive soon.
The conduit along the hillside is buried and the post for the meter and panel is up, so we&amp;rsquo;re hopeful the project will be completed without further delays after the boring is complete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seeking Your Feedback!</title>
      <link>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/seeking-feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/seeking-feedback/</guid>
      <description>Feedback is very important to help ensure we&amp;rsquo;re focusing on the right priorities and goals for the community.
Need some inspiration?
 Are monthly dues too high? Is rule enforcement too strict? Not strict enough? Any new rules or policies you would like to see? Any existing rules or policies that should be changed or removed? Any projects or improvements you would like to see around the neighborhood? Have a topic you&amp;rsquo;d like to discuss at the next meeting?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Board Seat Nominations - Spring 2021</title>
      <link>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/board-seat-nominations-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/board-seat-nominations-2021/</guid>
      <description>Each year, one or two seats on our board of directors expire and are up for election again. There are five seats total with each being for three year terms. The expirations are staggered by year. This year, there are two seats up for election.
 Matt Condio (elected 2019, expires 2022) Mary Duffy * (elected 2018, expires 2021) Geoff Kolton (elected 2019, expires 2022) Benn Linger * (elected 2018, expires 2021) Robb Williamson (elected 2020, expires 2023)  Emphasized above are the seats available for election this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mailbox Power Project Scheduled</title>
      <link>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/mailbox-power-project-scheduled/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/mailbox-power-project-scheduled/</guid>
      <description>Since convening in December, the board of directors has investigated getting lighting for our shared mailboxes as a top priority. Historically this has been more difficult than expected due to a lack of suitable connection points near the mailboxes for new electric service to be installed. After months of phone calls, appointments, e-mails, and site visits, the board has approved taking the first big step in moving toward this goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annual Meeting - Spring 2021</title>
      <link>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/annual-meeting-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/annual-meeting-2021/</guid>
      <description>Now that spring is upon us, the time for the annual meeting of our homeowners’ association is approaching.
The meeting is scheduled for Thursday, April 29 2021 at 7pm.
The board of directors has decided to hold the meeting virtually. This should allow for as many association members to comfortably attend as possible.
The meeting ended at 8pm. An audio recording of the meeting is available here.
The agenda is available here:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bulb Letters - Spring 2021</title>
      <link>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/bulb-letters-spring-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/bulb-letters-spring-2021/</guid>
      <description>Reminder letters will be sent out shortly to homeowners with lamp posts that have not been lit up at night.
As a friendly reminder: the lamp posts in front of individual houses are the primary source of light made available to those walking after dark in the neighborhood. Homeowners are responsible for ensuring they remain functional and with working bulbs for the safety and consistency of our community.
For those purchasing:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hillside Structural Assessments</title>
      <link>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/hillside-structural-assessments/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/hillside-structural-assessments/</guid>
      <description>Last month, the board investigated seeking the opinions of qualified engineers to assess the structural integrity of our hillside. While no imminent issues were expected to be found, it was deemed sufficiently within the interests of the homeowners&#39; association to at least pursue the costs and potential recommended remediation steps of any issues found. This has been a minor concern brought up at our last few in-person annual meetings.
I&amp;rsquo;m pleased to report we&amp;rsquo;ve now had two separate firms make on-site visits to assess, and both have acknowledged no significant concerns about the structural integrity of the hillside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dog Waste Station Available</title>
      <link>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/dog-waste-station-available/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/dog-waste-station-available/</guid>
      <description>The dog waste station has now been installed and is available for use.
The emptying schedule is currently set for Tuesdays and Fridays, although we&amp;rsquo;ll be keeping an eye on utilization to adjust as necessary. More details about the trial run can be found at the previous post here and the subsequent location update post here.
Picture of dog waste station as installed, January 2021.
If you have any questions or feedback, feel free to message me on Facebook, send me an e-mail (benn@bennlinger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dog Waste Station Trial Run Location Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/dog-waste-station-trial-location-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/dog-waste-station-trial-location-update/</guid>
      <description>In response to feedback, the board has agreed to revise the location of the dog waste station for the trial run announced previously. Its new location will be about sixty-five feet further from the mailboxes along the same sidewalk.
The green X represents the previous location. The red X is the new location.
Please also note that the fast-setting concrete mix necessary calls for an ambient temperature of at least 40°F for install, so I&amp;rsquo;ll be keeping an eye on the weather forecasts for a good day / time to install.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dog Waste Station Trial Run</title>
      <link>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/dog-waste-station-trial/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/dog-waste-station-trial/</guid>
      <description>The board has approved a trial run of a revival of the dog waste station previously installed in the neighborhood. I plan to install it over the next few days in roughly the same place as it was before. Dog waste stations are commonly found in nicer managed communities, so it&amp;rsquo;s our expectation that this is one small step we can take to help bolster the home values for all HOA members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Budget 2021 Chart</title>
      <link>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/budget-2021-chart/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/budget-2021-chart/</guid>
      <description>I put together a spreadsheet and pie chart to help show how much of our $75 monthly dues go to what expenses for the homeowners&#39; association. The data here is based on our 2021 budget.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the chart:
This basically involved grouping various categories from the budget to make it a little easier to understand. For more details, you can check out the spreadsheet behind the chart here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Board of Directors 2020-21</title>
      <link>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/board-members-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/board-members-2020/</guid>
      <description>Per the correspondence sent out earlier this month, we have a new member of our board of directors. The list of board members for this term is now:
 Matt Condio Mary Duffy Geoff Kolton Benn Linger Robb Williamson (newly elected)  The board also met earlier this month and made the following appointments:
 President: Benn Linger Vice President: Robb Williamson Secretary: Mary Duffy  Despite this year&amp;rsquo;s delayed annual meeting correspondence due to COVID-19, the board intends to resume the normal annual meeting schedule in the March - May timeframe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog Launched</title>
      <link>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/blog-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.prestleyheightstownhomes.org/posts/blog-launch/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve set up this simple blog as a place where news related to the Homeowners&#39; Association can be shared. Hopefully this should help with keeping the community informed of various happenings.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
